Guide to the Lydia Winston Malbin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Paintings, 1938-1982; Series I; (16 boxes)
  - Kandinsky, Wassily
    - "Luminosity", 1927 (#338), circa 1944 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Klee, Paul
    - "Forged Still Life", c. 1929, circa 1942 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - "Signs in Blue" (#3), circa 1947 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - "What Remains", 1937 (#131), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Krajcberg, J.
    - "Composition", 1959 (#119) Photograph only (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - "Composition" (large), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Le Fresnaye, Roger
    - "Study for the 14th of July" (#57) (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Leger, Fernand
    - "Woman in Armchair" (Box 9, Folder 83-85)
  - Lissitzky, El Markovitch
    - "Proun No.95", c.1920 (#81), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 86-87)
  - Louis, Morris
    - "Late Flowering", 1962 (#222), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - "Quo Numine Lasso", 1959 (#221), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 89-90)
  - Lucebert (L.G. Swanswijk)
    - "Family Portrait" (#185) (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - MacDonald-Wright, Stanton
    - "Conception [Synchrony]", 1914 (#94), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 92-93)
  - Magnelli, Alberto
    - Untitled Collage, 1949 (#48), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Marcoussis, Louis
    - "Loreley", 1932 (#159), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Marin, John
    - "Near Stonington, Maine", 1915 (#93), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - "Small Pointe, Maine", 1914 (#66), 1938 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Metzinger, Jean
    - "Still Life with Pears", 1912-17 (#151), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - "Still Life with Pipe", 1916 (#152), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Miro, Jean
    - "The Brothers Fratellini", 1927 (#80), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 100-101)
    - "Figure and Bird in Front of the Sun", 1930 (#68), 1948 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Mondrian, Piet
    - "Composition in Black and White with blue Square", 1935 (#71), 1947 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - "Composition in Black and White with Blue Square" (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Mortensen, Richard
    - "Cahier de Marseille IV" (gouache) (#230) 1959 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Noland, Kenneth
    - "Baba Yoggs" (Acrylic resin on canvas), 1964 (#223) (Box 12, Folder 106-107)
  - Paris, Harold
    - "Carta Series #44", 1975, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Pegeen
    - "Tea Party" (#215), 1945, articles only (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Pevsner, Antoine
    - "Square Relief", 1922 (#148), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Picabia, Francis
    - "Mechanical Expression...", 1913 (#35), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - "Paysage de la Creuse", c.1912 (#146), 1952 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - "Portrait of Marie Laurencin", c. 1917 (#43), 1952 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Catalog Raisonee (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Picasso, Pablo
    - "Glass on a Table", 1914 (#96), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - "Portrait of Dora Maar", 1941 (#98), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - "Still Life with Guitar", 1921, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Pindell, Howardena
    - "III Memory Test: Throne", 1980 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Pollock, Jackson
    - "Moon Vessel", 1945 (#124) (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Prampolini, Enrico
    - "Mechanical Venus" (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - "Polimaterico Automatismo A", 1940 (#40), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - "Polimaterico Automatismo C", 1940 (#41), 1958 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - "Polimaterico Automatismo F", 1940 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert
    - Lists, articles, etc (Box 14, Folder 124-125)
  - Russell, Morgan
    - "Synchrony #2, To Light" 1912, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 126-127)
  - Russolo, Luigi
    - "Perfume", 1909, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Schwitters, Kurt
    - "C 48 S.Y. Cut-Merz" 1946 (#46) 1948 [?] (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - "Composition: Ashoff, Ellen", 1922, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - "Ent Garrett, Merz", 1947, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - "Examiner 2861, Merz" (collage), 1947, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - "S 55 Merz" (collage), 1946 (sold as C 55 Merz") (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Severini, Gino
    - "Dance Beside the Sea", 1913 (#5), 1951 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - "Portrait of Mme. S." (pastel), 1912 (#4) (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - "Portrait of Madame Severini" (watercolor), 1913 (#6), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - "Still Life with Cherries", 1913 (#8), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - "Still Life with Epinette", (#11), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - Other works by Severini (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - Three Documents Pertaining to First Futurist Exhibition (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Sironi, Mario
    - "Composition", 1912 (#28) (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - "The Dance" (gouache), 1913 (#30) (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - "Man on the Motorcycle", 1918 (#32) (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Sottsass, Ettore, Jr.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Stael, Nicolas de
    - "Abstraction", 1950 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - Stella, Frank
    - "Sketch Red Lead", 1964 (#227) (Box 15, Folder 146-147)
  - Mark Tobey
    - "Battle of the Lights" (gouache), 1954 (#49), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - "Battle of the Lights" (gouache), 1954 (#49), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 149)
  - Tonkonow, Leslie
    - "Broken Glass", 1982 (Box 16, Folder 150)
    - "Table", 1981, 1982 (Box 16)
    - "Triangle", 1982 (Box 16)
  - Torres Garcia, Joaquin
    - "Symmetrical Composition", 1931 (#86), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 151-152)
  - Turbyfill, Mark
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - Vasarely, Victor de
    - "Ixion", ca.1964 (#226) (Box 16, Folder 154-155)
  - Warhol, Andy
    - "Self-Portrait", 1967 (Box 16, Folder 156)
  - Wilt, Richard
    - (Oil) (#239), Clipping only (Box 16, Folder 157)
  - Xceron, Jean
    - "Composition #196B" (watercolor on paper), 1944 (#270), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 158)
- Sculpture, 1949-1982; Series II; (8.5 boxes)
  This series consists of documentation for sculptures in Malbin's art collection. For each work, files include: documentation concerning how the art work was obtained, research, negotiations, arrangement for shipment, and notes; photographs; conservation records; correspondence with the artist and with the family, regarding the work and requests to sell; exhibition records; publication record; use by scholars; gallery materials, including brochures and catalogs; other works by the artist; and secondary materials, regarding the work, regarding the artist, and/or regarding the particular art movement.
  - Arp, Jean
    - "Bird Forms", 1922 (#140), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - "Composition", ca. 1954-55 (#144), 1956 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - "Dream Column", 1938, 1958 (#141) (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - "Ganemede", 1958 (Box 17, Folder 162)
    - "Lunar Armor", 1938 (#139) (Box 17, Folder 163-164)
    - Arp's Essay, "Speculations Serieuses et Droles", circa 1957, and photographs (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - Balla, Giacomo
    - "Fist of Boccioni - Lines of Force", 1915, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 166-167)
    - "Rose", ca. 1920-25 (#36), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - "Tree", ca. 1920-25 (#37), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Boccioni, Umberto
    - "Antigrazioso," 1912 (#20), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 170-171)
    - "The Bottle in Space", 1912 (#26), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 172)
    - "Unique Forms of Continuity in Space", 1913 (#24), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 173-174)
    - Boccioni's Palette, gift-1959 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - Brancusi, Constantin
    - "The Blond Negress", 1926 (#127), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 176-178)
    - "The Blond Negress": "The Picasso Tale (Tail) and Brancusi Amour", a play by Harry and Lydia Winston (Box 19, Folder 179)
  - Bulone, Joseph D.
    - "Harlequin Nude", 1976 (#286), 1982 (Box 19, Folder 180)
  - Calder, Alexander
    - Mobile, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 181-183)
  - Callery, Mary
    - "Exposition Sculpture", 1949, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 184)
  - Capralos, Christos
    - "The Poet and His Muse", 1960 (#182), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 185)
    - "Zeus and Hera", 1961 (#181), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 186)
  - Cesar
    - "L'Oiseau De Fer", 1957, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 187)
  - Consagra, Pietro
    - "Colloquies", 1959 (Box 20, Folder 188)
    - Catalogs (Box 20, Folder 189)
  - Dalwood, Hubert
    - "King", 1960 (#179), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 190)
    - "Object", 1959 (Box 20, Folder 191)
  - Distel, Herbert
    - "Breakfast Egg", 1969, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 192)
  - Dorazio, Piero
    - "Abstract" (#42), 1958 (Box 20, Folder 193)
    - "Ubiquita", 1955, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 194)
  - Dubuffet, Jean
    - "La Folatre", 1954 (Box 20, Folder 195)
  - Duchamp, Marcel
    - "Please Touch" (Book cover), 1947 (Box 20, Folder 196)
    - "Valise", 1941-42, 1952 (#145) (Box 21, Folder 197-198)
    - Secondary material (Box 21, Folder 199)
  - Freeley, Paul
    - "Dabih" (Box 21, Folder 200)
  - Fontana, Lucio
    - "Study for Doors of the Milan Cathedral" (#187) (Box 21, Folder 201)
  - Gabo, Naum
    - "Linear Construction in Space No.2", ca. 1950 (#149), 1952 (Box 21, Folder 202)
  - Gilioli, Emile
    - "La Chimere", 1956 (Box 21, Folder 203)
  - Gonzalez, Julio
    - "The Kiss", 1930, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 204-205)
    - "Woman with a Broom", 1930, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 206)
  - Hajou, Etienne
    - "The Bud", 1949, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 207)
    - "The Siren" (Box 22, Folder 208)
  - Hoflehner, Rudolf
    - "Dea Mediterranea", 1958, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 209)
  - Kotchar, Ervand
    - "Figure", 1932 (#95), 1956 (Box 22, Folder 210)
  - Kulak, Gary
    - "G-Cleff", 1980 (Box 22, Folder 211)
  - La Chaise, Gaston
    - "Woman - Arms Akimbo", 1910, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - "Woman Arranging Hair", 1956 (Box 23, Folder 213)
  - Laurens, Henri
    - "Man with a Moustache", 1917, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 214)
  - Lee, Caroline
    - "La Bouee", 1971 (#246) (Box 23, Folder 215)
  - Meadows, Bernard
    - "Shot Bird", 1958 (#53), 1959 (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - "Shot Bird", 1959 (#54) (Box 23, Folder 217)
  - Milles, Carl
    - "Angel with a Flute", c. 1920 (#155), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 218)
  - Moore, Henry
    - Abstract Sculpture, 1937 (#154), 1959 (Box 23, Folder 219)
    - Works Not Purchased (Box 23, Folder 220)
  - Nakian, Rueben
    - "Nymph and Goat", c. 1960, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 221)
  - Neri, Manuel
    - "Head", 1975 (#252), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 222)
  - Nevelson, Louise
    - "Personage One Plus Two", c. 1947 (#116), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 223)
  - Packard, David
    - "Balled Head", 1962 (#189) (Box 24, Folder 224)
  - Park, Chong Bae
    - Cast Iron Sculpture No. 25, 1967, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 225)
  - Pevsner, Antoine
    - "Fauna of the Ocean", 1944, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 226-227)
    - "Figure", 1925 (#147) (Box 24, Folder 228)
  - Richier, Germaine
    - "The Six-Headed Horse", 1953-56 (#195), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 229)
  - Rosso, Medardo
    - "The Flesh of Others", 1883 (#219), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    - "Jewish Boy", 1892 (#218), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 231)
    - "Man in Hospital", 1880 (#216), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - "Sick Boy", 1893 (#217), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 233)
    - Other Works Not in Collection, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 234)
  - Schoffer, Nicolas
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - Smith, Tony (plywood mock-ups)
    - "New Piece" (Box 25, Folder 236)
    - "Polyhedron", 1970 (Box 25, Folder 237)
    - "Spitball", 1961/70 (#153), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 238)
  - Torres Garcia, Joaquin
    - "Composition", 1928, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 239)
  - Tullis, Garner
    - "Recycled Painting" (#254), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 240)
  - Vail, Lawrence
    - "Figure No.1", n.d.; and "Figure No. 2", n.d. (#164, #165), 1956 (Box 25, Folder 241)
- Graphics, 1944-1988; Series III; (9.5 boxes)
  This series consists of documentation for graphic works in Malbin's art collection. For each work, files include: documentation concerning how the art work was obtained, research, negotiations, arrangement for shipment, and notes; photographs; conservation records; correspondence with the artist and with the family, regarding the work and requests to sell; exhibition records; publication record; use by scholars; gallery materials, including brochures and catalogs; other works by the artist; and secondary materials, regarding the work, regarding the artist, and/or regarding the particular art movement.
  The files within this series are largely arranged alphabetically by artist.
  - General
    - Graphics List (Box 25, Folder 242)
    - Graphics Invoices (Box 25, Folder 243)
    - Prints (miscellaneous) (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - AFFICHE: Poster Inventory (1981 Jun); List of Posters from Winston Collection exhibited at UCLA Art Galleries; Complete list (1970 Jan - 1973); Posters, Unmounted (1971); Affiche, Large unmounted; Affiche, Acetate mountings: Rubiner Gallery; Affiche for B.A.A.; Affiches in the Winston Malbin Collection (1981);Miscellaneous lists, 1971-1981 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Artists as illustrators (Box 25, Folder 246)
  - Adam, Jacob
    - Greeting (colored lithograph & collage) (#G-216) (Box 25, Folder 247)
  - Albers, Anni
    - "Triadic Series" (serigraphs):"C" (#G-591), 1969;"D" (#G-592), 1969; "E" (#G-593), 1969; "F" (#G-594), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 248)
  - Albers, Josef
    - "Homages to the Square: LXXa, LXXb" or "Commemorative", [1970?] (Box 25, Folder 249)
    - "Homages to the Square: Soft Edge - Hard Edge" (10 lithographs), 1965 (#G-380) (Box 25, Folder 250)
    - Interaction of Color (book) (Box 25, Folder 251)
    - Portfolio: "Ten Variants", 1966 1967 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - "Ten Variants", 1966 1969/70 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - "Seclusion" (lithograph: 19/30) 1959 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - "Solo V" (intaglio) (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - Albers: Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 256)
  - Alechinsky, Pierre
    - "Personages" (colored lithograph) (#G-213) (Box 26, Folder 257)
  - Antreasian, Garo
    - "Illus. from 'Fragments'" (G#-366) note only (Box 26, Folder 258)
  - Apollinaire, Guillaume
    - "Il pleut", 1930 (#G-267) (Box 26, Folder 259)
  - Appel, Karel
    - "Flying Birds" (colored lithograph) (#G-214) (Box 26, Folder 260)
    - "Composition" (colored lithograph), 1958 (#G-315), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 261)
    - "Composition" (colored lithograph), 1959 (#G-314), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 262)
  - Archipenko, Alexander
    - "Still Life" (lithograph), c.1912 (#G-22) (Box 26, Folder 263)
  - Arp, Jean; Delaunay, Sonia; Magnelli, Alberto; Taeuber-Arp, Sophie
    - Collaboration (portfolio: 10 colored lithographs: 129/165), 1942/1950 (#G-151), 1960 (Box 26, Folder 264)
  - Arp, Jean
    - "La Magie Quotidienne" (woodcut: 42/70), 1961 (#G-575), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 265)
    - Papier Dechire (collage, black on beige paper), n.d. (#231) [folder contains photographs of LWM visiting Arp's studio] (Box 26, Folder 266)
    - Untitled (affiche) (#G-620), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 267)
    - Untitled (etching: 45/50) (#G-723) (Box 26, Folder 268)
  - Baertling, Olle
    - Serigraphs from the album, "The Angles of Baertling": "No.I", 1955-68 (#G-552); "No.II", 1965-68 (#G-553); "No.III", 1965-68 (#G-554), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Baro, Gene
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - Baumeister, Willi
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - Benton, Fletcher
    - "Circle and Incline Series IV", 1975 (#G-794), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - Bisserie, Roger
    - "Rose" (color etching: 52/60) (#G-38) [1968?] (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - Bobbitt, Vernon
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - Buckley, Stephen
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 275)
  - Boccioni, Umberto - Etchings
    Related Archival Materials note
    See Boccioni Drawings & Etchings
  - Bonnard, Pierre
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - Broner, Robert
    - "Quarry Print" 1962 (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - Brulc, Dennis
    - "Andy's Change" (print) (#G-627) [information only] (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Calder, Alexander
    - "Flying Saucers"
      See Gifts
    - "Mobiles de Calder" (affiche-lithograph) (Box 26, Folder 279)
  - Callery, Mary
    - "Study for Sculpture" (lithograph & hand painted: 47/48), 1953 (#G-564), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 280)
  - Campigli, Massimo
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 281)
  - Capogrossi, Giuseppe
    - Lithographs. Portfolio. (#G-146) (Box 26, Folder 282)
  - Caulfield, Patrick
    - "Verres et Bouteille" (serigraph), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 283)
  - Cesar, Baldacchini
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 284)
  - Chew, Teng Beng
    - "Conglomeration 1969" (lithograph) (Box 26, Folder 285)
  - Chillida, Eduardo
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Christo (Christo Javacheff)
    - "Corridor Store Front" (lithograph & plexiglass: 19/75) (#G-588) (Box 27, Folder 287)
  - Claisse, Genevieve
    - "Cercles" (serigraphs), 1967 (#G-567), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - Colla, Ettore
    - "La Lithografia ... Argan" (portfolio) (#G-364) Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 289)
  - Corneille (Cornelis van Beverloe)
    - "Jeux d'ete" (lithograph - colored) (#G-209) (Box 27, Folder 290)
    - "Mer du Sud" (litho) (#G-210) (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - Couzijn, Wessel
    - "Composition No. 1" (lithograph), 1963 (#G-313); "Composition No. 2" (lithograph), (#G-312); "Composition No. 3" (lithograph), 1963 (#G-311); notes only (Box 27, Folder 292)
    - "Moving Forms" (etching) (#G-215) (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Dagan, Geula
    - (#G-124): Note only (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - D'Archangelo, Alan
    - "Landscape" (serigraph) (#G-549), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Davie, Alan
    - "Zurich Improvisations No. 17" (litho-color: 23/25), n.d. (#G-577) (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - Day, John
    - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 297)
  - Delaunay, Sonia
    - "Composition" (litho-color: 25/25), n.d. (#G-28) (Box 27, Folder 298)
  - De Marco, Hugo
    - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Denis, Maurice
    - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Derain, Andre
    - "The Last Supper" (drypoint: 30/60) (#G-2) (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Dine, Jim
    - "Affiche" (litho): information only (#G-725) (Box 27, Folder 302)
    - "Colored Palette" (colored litho), 1963: information only (#G-342) (Box 27, Folder 303)
    - "Toothbrushes #4" (litho), 1962, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - Dorazio, Piero
    - "Documenta III" (litho), 1964 (#G-517), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 305)
    - Untitled (#G-415), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 306)
  - Duchamp, Marcel
    - "The Bride Stripped Bare" (poster) (#G-726), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 307)
    - "Infernal Machine", 1952 (#G-329); corres and articles only, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 308)
    - "Self-Portrait Profile", 1961: photographs only (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - Ellis, Robert C.
    - "Extinguished" (woodcut: 6/10) (#G-23) (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - Ernst, Jimmy
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Ernst, Max
    - "Les Chiens Ont Soif" (book containing etchings) (#G-75) (Box 28, Folder 312)
    - "Foret" (lithograph color: 1/200) (#G-26) (Box 28, Folder 313)
    - "Histoire Naturelle" (prints), 1926 [late 1930's] (Box 28, Folder 314)
    - "Three Heads" (lithograph color) (#G-10) (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Esteve, Maurice
    - "Aladin" (lithograph color: 40/125), 1958 (#G-25) (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Fiorini, Giosetta
    - (#G-103): Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen
    - "Sky Frame IV" (monotype color), 1964 (#G-373) (Box 28, Folder 318)
    - "What Red Lines Can Do" (silkscreen), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Frasconi, Antonio
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Freundlich, Otto
    - Untitled (woodcut), 1921 (#G-897), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Gabo, Naum
    - Poster: invoice only (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Gannon, Penelope
    - Untitled (serigraph color: 19/300), 1972 (#G-688) (Box 28, Folder 323)
  - Geiger, Rupprecht
    - "Untitled" (Box 28, Folder 324)
  - Giacommetti, Alberto
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 325)
  - Gosling, Enid
    - "Trees-Quebec II" (etching) (#G-369) Article only (Box 28, Folder 326)
  - Greaver, Hanne
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 327)
  - Haden, Sir Seymour
    - "Water Meadow" (Box 28, Folder 328)
  - Hamilton, Richard
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 329)
  - Hayter, Stanley William
    - "Abstraction" (intaglio, color: 52/2000) (#G-9), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 330)
  - Heizer, Michael
    - Poster (#G-669) (Box 29, Folder 331)
  - Held, Al
    - "Untitled I" (serigraph: 1966/68) (#G-551), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 332)
  - Hirtzel, Sue Carol
    - "Black Set 2" (intaglio: 2/6), 1972 (#G-756) (Box 29, Folder 333)
  - Hockney, David
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 334)
  - Hodgkin, Howard
    - "Bedroom" (color litho: 14/75), 1966 (#G-319); "Girl on Sofa" (col, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 335)
  - Hoffman, Hans
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 336)
  - Honegger, Gottfried
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 337)
  - Honegger-Lavater, Warja
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 338)
  - Indiana, Robert
    - "Love" (serigraph, color) (#G-572), 1969 (Box 29, Folder 339)
  - Jenkins, Louisa
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 340)
  - Johns, Jasper
    - "Hatteras" (lithograph) (#G-363) (Box 29, Folder 341)
  - Jones, Allen
    - "Slipper" (litho) (#G-626), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 342)
  - Kandinsky, Wassily
    - "Blau" (Box 29, Folder 343)
    - "Klange" (woodcut), 1912 (#g-252) (Box 29, Folder 344)
    - "Klein Welten" Series: "Klein Welten I" (lithograph color), 1922, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 345-346)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth
    - "Cyclamen III" (litho: 18/75), 1964 (#G-573) (Box 30, Folder 347)
    - "No. 4 Vert" (lithograph color: 40/75), 1964 (#G-574) (Box 30, Folder 348)
  - Koutroulis, Aris
    - Untitled (clichè verre) (#G-660) (Box 30, Folder 349)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo
    - "Acrobat" (lithograph) (#G-14) (Box 30, Folder 350)
    - "Still Life at the Window" (lithograph: 15/25), 1928 (#G-20) (Box 30, Folder 351)
  - (After) Laurencin, Marie
    - "Two Girls and a Dog" (lithograph/copy) (#G-21) (Box 30, Folder 352)
  - Le Parc, Julio
    - "Black & White Circles" (lithograph color: 109/125) or Planche No., 1969 (Box 30, Folder 353)
    - "Black & White Circles" (lithograph color: 60/125) or Planche No. I, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 354)
  - Levine, Les
    - 3 clear "Disposables" (acrylite) (#G-606), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 355)
    - 9 small "Disposables" (acrylite - many colors) (#G-608), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 356)
    - "Waterdrop" (plastic) (#G-607), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 357)
    - "Iris Printout Portrait" (portfolio of 9 photographs, 4 color: 8/8, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 358)
  - Lieberman, Alexander
    - Untitled (BA# 31) (lithograph color: 64/90), 1969; Untitled (BA# 3, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 359)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy
    - "Head of a Girl" (lithograph color) (#G-479) (Box 30, Folder 360)
    - "Stedelijk" (lithograph color) (#G-585), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 361)
  - Lindstrom, Bengt
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 362)
  - Longo, Vincent
    See also Greetings
    - "Center: Grid" (etching), 1964 (#G-445)
      See "Swinging White"
    - "Frontal" (etchings: gray 2/45, plum 33/45, green 2/45), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 363)
    - "Green Screen" (etching), 1967
    - "Keeping Still" (etching), 1964
    - "Other Side" (etching), 1967
    - "Plaid" (etching & aquatint), 1968, notes and correspondence only, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 364)
    - "Round Form" (etching), 1966
    - "Screen" (etching), 1967
    - "Swinging White" (woodcut: 2/15), 1958 (Box 30, Folder 365)
  - Lucebert (L. G. Swanswijk)
    - "Geheime Raad" (etching) (#G-212) (Box 30, Folder 366)
  - Magritte, Rene
    - "Feet of Magritte" (poster) (#G-754) (Box 30, Folder 367)
  - Maillol, Aristide
    - "Nude Sitting" (woodcut, from L'Art D'Aimer), 1935 (#G-248) [1968] (Box 30, Folder 368)
  - Marini, Marino
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 369)
  - Martyka, Paul
    - "171 Cubes" (intaglio, color), 1972 (#G-750) (Box 30, Folder 370)
    - "Mythology of Being: A Poem" (#G-260), 1945 (Box 30, Folder 371)
    - "Nocturnal Notebooks", 1944, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 372)
  - Max, Peter
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 373)
  - Merida, Carlos
    - "Estampas del Popol Vuh" (portfolio of 10 color lithographics), 19 (Box 31, Folder 374)
  - Michaux, Henri
    - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 375)
  - Miro, Joan